Damian Dubciuc

+ (373) 68 779 861 • ddubciuc@gmail.com

Software/Web Developer with 1 year of experience from both studies and work. Handsome guy with a deepen love for math, physics and algorithms. A passionate guitar singer, billiards player and late night drive enjoyer. Eager to learn new technologies and interact with wholesome people.

Experience

FEBRUARY 2023 - MAY 2023

WEB Academy | Front End | Advanced CSS

> Used technologies: Node, HTML, SCSS, Safari, Chrome, JetBrains WebStorm, MacOS, Windows

JUNE 2023 - ONGOING

WEB Academy | Front End | Advanced JS

> Used technologies: Node, HTML, Safari, Chrome, JetBrains WebStorm, JS, MacOS

MAY 2023

WEB Academy | Front End | Website

> Used technologies: Figma, CSS, HTML, JetBrains WebStorm, Github, Warp, Mozila, Safari, MacOS

JULY 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

TERITORIUL DL | Front End | Website

tdl.md

> Used technologies: JS, SCSS, HTML, Github, JetBrains WebStorm, Warp, Safari, Chrome, Mozila, Windows, MacOS

FEBRUARY 2023

UTM | Web Parsing

> Used technologies: Python, Warp, JetBrains PyCharm, MacOS

APRIL 2023

UTM | Electric Circuit Converter/Calculator App

> Used technologies: Java, JetBrains IntelliJ, JavaFX, MacOS

APRIL 2023

UTM | Password Hashing App

> Used technologies: Python, JetBrains PyCharm, Warp, MacOS

SEPTEMBER- DECEMBER 2023

UTM | Automobile price analysis and prediction

> Used technologies: R (programming language), Safari, MacOS, Warp

JANUARY 2024- ONGOING

Personal | Angular project

> Used technologies: Node.js, HTML, SCSS, Safari, MacOS, Angular, Visiual Studio Code, Docker, PostgreSQL

FEBRUARY 2024 - APRIL 2024

Esempla System | Front End | Internship Project

> Used technologies: Node.js, HTML, SCSS, Safari, Chrome, MacOS, Windows, Angular, Visiual Studio Code, Docker, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, Swagger

JANUARY 2024 - APRIL 2024

UTM | Android application for detecting vision defects

> Used technologies: Android Studio, XML, Java, MacOS, Safari, Android SDK

Spoken languages

Romanian - Native • Russian - C2 • English - B1• French - C1

Education

SEPTEMBER 2021 - ONGOING

Applied Informatics | UTM | Moldova

FEBRUARY 2023 - AUGUST 2023

HTML, CSS, JS | WEB ACADEMY | Moldova

FEBRUARY 2024 - APRIL 2024

Internship Front End | Esempla System | Moldova